Guide to the Yale School of Drama Photographs and Posters
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale School of Drama photographs and posters
1920-2003
RU 397
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
42.75
The materials consist of photographs, posters, and renderings of set designs and contact sheets documenting Yale School of Drama productions, including performances at the Yale Repertory Theatre, events, and individuals.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 22-H (YRG 22-H), Photographs, audio-visual materials, and memorabilia documenting the Yale School of Drama.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The pictures are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs, posters, and renderings of set designs and contact sheets documenting Yale School of Drama productions, including performances at the Yale Repertory Theatre, events, and individuals..
Acting -- Study and teaching; College theater; Drama -- Study and teaching; Theater; Photographs; Yale Repertory Theatre; Yale School of Drama
- Photographs of Yale School of Drama productions, circa 1920-1939; Series I
  - Productions
    - 1927-1933
      - Peking Politics, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Chastelard, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Parade, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - She Stoops to Compromise, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Spring O'the Year, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - No More Frontier, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Man and the Masses, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Pueblo, circa 1930 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - The Revisiting Affair, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - The Searcher, costume designs, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - The Searcher, set designs (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Emperor Jones, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - People on the Hill, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Steel, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Tom Tyler and His Wife, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Trial by Jury, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - The Trodinian Maidens, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - The Winter's Tale, characters, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - The Winter's Tale, scenes (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Murder in the Cathedral, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Circa 1920's- 1930's
      - All People (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - "Bound East for Cardiff' (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - "Brand" (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Brief Candle (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Chanticleer-Rosalind (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - The Cherry Orchard (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Dracula (?) (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - King's Coat (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Lottie Gathers no Moss (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Merry-Go-Round (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - ''Natural Magic" (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Orpheus (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Overlords, scene (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Overlords, sets (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - The Provincials (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Venice Preserved (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - What's a Fixer For? (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Abbey Players (British Company) at Yale, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Sets of Ralph Roister Doister and Jack Rabbit Flats, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous set designs and productions, circa 1930s (Box 1, Folder 40 - 41)
  - Mr. Griswold, circa 1930s (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - OVERSIZE
    - Production photographs (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Photographs, 1956, 1967; Accession 19ND-A-456
  - Productions, 1956 (Box 1)
  - "The Making of Prometheus", 1967 (Box 1)
  - "The Drama School Unbound", 1967 (Box 1)
  - Newsweek photographs (Box 1)
  - Time photographs (Box 1)
- Yale Repertory Theatre production photographs, 1990; Accession 1990-A-156
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1990 (Box 1)
- Yale Repertory Theatre photographs, circa 1985- 1991; Accession 1994-A-076
  - Elizabeth, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Sarcophagus, circa 1987 (Box 1)
  - Vampires in Kodachrome, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Unlabeled performance and cast shots, Undated (Box 1)
  - Ivanov, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Starting Monday, circa 1989 (Box 1)
  - Interrogating the Nude, circa 1989 (Box 1)
  - The Beach, circa 1989 (Box 1)
  - Phaedra and Hippolytus, circa 1989 (Box 1)
- Rendering of the Yale School of Drama's production of "Sleeping Beauty," by Donald B. Tirrell (1954), undated; Accession 2002-A-205
  - Rendering of the Yale School of Drama's production of "Sleeping Beauty", by Donald B. Tirrell, Class of 1954, undated (Box 1)
- Photographic contact sheets from theatrical productions at the Yale Repertory Theatre, 1967-2002; Accession 2003-A-125
  - William B. Carter
    - About Face, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
    - Ah, Wilderness, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
    - Almost by chance a woman: Elizabeth, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
    - T. Charles Erikson (Box 1)
    - The America Play, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
    - The Adventures Of Amy Bock, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
    - Antigone in New York, 1994-1995 (Box 1)
    - Apocalyptic Butterflies, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
    - Are You Now or Have you Ever Been, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
    - As You Like It, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
    - Astapovo, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - As You Like It, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - An Attempt at Flying, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
    - Baal, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
    - Bacchae, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - The Baltimore Waltz, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Banquet Years, 1977 (Box 1)
    - The Beauty Part, 1962 (Box 1)
    - The Beaux's Strategem, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Beef, No Chicken, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Big House, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Bingo, 1976 (Box 1)
    - The Blood Knot, 1986 May (Box 1)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - Boesman and Lenna, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
    - Bosoms and Neglect, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - William Baker
    - Bourgeois Gentlemen, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
    - A Break in the Skin, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
    - Bricklayers, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
    - The Bundle, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Buried Child, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Caligula, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
    - Cemetery Club, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
    - A Child's Tale, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
    - Chopin in Space, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
    - Clutch, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - The Colored Museum, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
    - Coriolanus, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - William B. Carter
    - Coyote Ugly, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
    - Crazy from the Heart, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
    - Crimes and Crimes, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - The Cryptogram, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - The Curse of the Starving Class, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
  - William Baker
    - The Dark Room, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
    - The Day of the Picnic, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
    - Daylight in Exile, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
    - Death of the Last Black Man (Winterfest), 1991-1992 (Box 2)
    - Democracy in America (Winterfest), 1991-1962 (Box 2)
    - Dinosaurs (Winterfest), 1989-1990 (Box 2)
    - A Doll House, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - Domestic Issues (Winterfest), 1980-1981 (Box 2)
    - Don Juan, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Nick Zavalighin
    - Don Juan, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Joe Cazalet
    - Dynamite Tonight, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
    - Durango Flash, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
    - Edward II, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Richard Anderson
    - Escape from Happiness, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
    - Exact Change, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
    - The Father, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
    - Faulkner's Bicycle (Winterfest), 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Fefu and her Friends (Winterfest), 1991-1992 (Box 3)
    - Fences, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Figaro Figaro, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
    - First Lady, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
    - Flash Floods, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - The Frogs, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Bruce Siddons
    - General Gorgeous, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - William Baker
    - Geography of a Horse Dreamer, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - Ghost Sonata, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
    - God Bless, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - Going Over (Winterfest), 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - Gov't Inspector, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
    - Great Chinese Revolution, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - Great Shot, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - Hamlet, 1992-1993 (Box 3)
    - Happy End, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
    - Heartbreak House, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - Hedda Gabler, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
  - Enrico
    - Henry IV, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
    - Henry IV part I, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Hello and Goodbye, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - Idiots Karamazov, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
    - I married you for the fun of it, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - Intermezzo, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Importance of Being Earnest, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - In the Clap Shack, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
    - Ivanov, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Joe Turners' Come and Gone, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Johnny Bull, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - Julius Caesar, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
    - Kiss of the Spider Woman, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - Landscape of the Body, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
    - Largo Desolato, 1960-1961 (Box 4)
    - Lear, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - A Lesson from Aloes, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - Le Bourgeois Avant-Garde, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
    - Life is a Dream, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
    - Little Eyolf, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
    - The Little Mahogany, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
    - Long Days Journey into the Night, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
    - Love's Labour's Lost, 1981-1982 (Box 4)
    - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
    - Macbeth, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
    - Magnificent Cuckold, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
    - Mahogany: A Chamber Version, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
    - Measure for Measure, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - Melons, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
    - The Memento (Winterfest), 1986-1987 (Box 4)
    - Metamorphoses, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - Eugene Cook
    - A Midsummer's Nights Dream, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
    - The Mirror, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
    - The Miser, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
    - Miss Julie, 1989-1990 (Box 4)
    - Mistaken Identities, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
    - Moon for the Misbegotten, 1961 (Box 4)
    - Mr. Puntilla and His Chauffer, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1981-1982 (Box 4)
    - Much Ado about Nothing, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
    - My Children! My Africa!, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
    - Major Barbara, 1983-1984 (Box 5)
    - Man is Man, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
    - Man who could see through time, 1981-1982 (Box 5)
    - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 1983-1984 (Box 5)
    - Marriage, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
    - Master Harold and the boys, 1981-1982 (Box 5)
    - Miss Julie, 1989/1990 (Box 5)
    - Neapolitan Ghosts, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
    - Night is Mother to the Day, 1983-1984 (Box 5)
    - The 1940's Radio Hour, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
    - Ohio State Murders (Winterfest), 1991/1991 (Box 5)
    - Oleanna, 1993/1994 (Box 5)
    - On the Verge, 1991/1992 (Box 5)
    - Othello, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
    - Passion, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
  - William B. Carter
    - The Philanderer, 1982-1983 (Box 5)
    - Piano Lesson, 1987-1988 (Box 5)
    - Pill Hill, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - A Place with the Pigs, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - Pentecost, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
    - Playing in Local Bands (Winterfest), 1982-1983 (Box 6)
    - The Possessed, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
    - Prometheus Bound, 1966-1967 (Box 6)
    - Pygmalion, 1959-1960 (Box 6)
    - Play of the Giants, 1984-1985 (Box 6)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - Playboy of the West Indies, 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - A Raisin in the Sun, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
    - Reunion, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
    - Resurrection of Lady Lester (Winterfest), 1980-1981 (Box 6)
    - Rip Van Winkle, 1981-1982 (Box 6)
    - Richard II, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
    - Rivals, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Road to Mecca, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
    - Rum and Coke, 1984-1985 (Box 6)
    - Rust and Ruin, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - St. Joan of stockyards, 1992-1993 (Box 6)
    - Sally and Marsha (Winterfest), 1980-1981 (Box 6)
    - Sarcophagus, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
    - Saved, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Scapin, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
    - School of Wives, 1993-1994 (Box 6)
    - Search and Destroy, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
    - Slavs!, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
    - The Skin of our Teeth, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - The Suicide, 1980-1981 (Box 6)
    - Suicide in Bb, 1976-1977 (Box 6)
    - Sweet Life, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
    - Sea Gull, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
    - Sganarelle, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
    - Shaft of Love, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
    - Schlemiel the 1st, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
    - Size of World, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
    - Stitchers and Starlight Talkers, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
    - Summer and Smoke, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
    - Solid Gold Cadillac, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
    - Story Theatre, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
    - Story Theatre Repertory, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
    - Tally's Folly, 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Paul J. Penders
    - Tartuffe, 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - William Baker
    - The Tempest, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
    - Terra Nova, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - Thunder Knocking on the Door, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
    - Ties that Bind, 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - Gerry Goodstein
    - They are Dying out, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
  - Barry Ford- Gerry Goodstein
    - Timon of Athens, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
  - H. Grossman
    - 'Tis Pity She's a Whore, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - Transformations, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
    - Touch of Poet, 1982-1983 (Box 7)
    - Trolius and Cressida, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
    - Trolius and Cressida, 1975-1976 (Box 7)
    - Tubs, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
    - Twelfth Night, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
    - Twelfth Night, 1980-1981 (Box 7)
    - Two Trains Running, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
    - Ubu Rex, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Uncle Vanya, 1994-1995 (Box 8)
  - Kirsten Beck
    - Uncle Vanya, 1981-1982 (Box 8)
    - Underground, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
    - Union Boys (Winterfest), 1985-1986 (Box 8)
    - Vampires in Codachrome (Winterfest), 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - T. Charles Erikson
    - Venus, 1995-1996 (Box 8)
    - Victory, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
    - Vietnamization of NJ, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
    - A Walk in the Woods, 1986-1987 (Box 8)
    - Walk the Dog, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
    - Warrior Ant (Box 8)
  - William Baker
    - Watergate Classics, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Henry Grossman
    - We Bombed in New Haven, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
    - What the Butler Saw, 1984-1985 (Box 8)
    - When We Dead Awaken, 1971-1972 (Box 8)
    - Where has Tommy Flowers gone?, 1970-1971 (Box 8)
    - The Winter's Tale, 1986-1987 (Box 8)
- Contact prints and slides of theatrical productions, 1975-1999; Accession 2003-A-156
  - Galileo, Paul J. Penders, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - God's Smoke, 1980 (Box 1)
  - The Golem, T. Charles Erikson, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - Goodperson of Szechwan, T. Charles Erikson, 1994-1995 (Box 1)
  - Goodperson of Szechwan, T. Charles Erikson, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - The Great Highway, T. Charles Erikson (Box 1)
  - Great Men of Science, T. Charles Erikson, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - Hamlet Del Valle, P. J. Penders, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Hamlet, P. J. Penders, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Happy End, T. Charles Erikson, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Help Wanted, P. J. Penders, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - The Hostage, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - House of York, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Imperceptible Mutabilities, T. Charles Erikson (Box 1)
  - Jungle of Cities, 1980 (Box 1)
  - King John (Box 1)
  - L'Aiglon (Box 1)
  - Learned Ladies, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Life is a Dream, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Life is a Dream, T. Charles Erikson, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - Long Days Journey into Night, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
  - Lorenzaccio, P. J. Penders, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Love of Three Oranges, T. Charles Erikson, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Lower Depths, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Mad Dog Blues, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - Measure for Measure, P. J. Penders, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Medea, T. Charles Erikson, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Midsummer, P. J. Penders, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Mississippi Nude, P. J. Penders, 1990 (Box 2)
  - The Misanthrope, T. Charles Erikson (Box 2)
  - Nabo, P. J. Penders, 1991 (Box 2)
  - The Name Of Oedipus, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Pacific Overtures, P. J. Penders, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Peer Gynt, T. Charles Erikson, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Peer Gynt, Margaret Glaser, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - People vs. God of Vengeance, T. Charles Erikson (Box 2)
  - Pericles, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - Pericles, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Pilgrims of the Night, T. Charles Erikson, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
  - Pillars of Society, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Platanov, P.J. Penders, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - The Pope and the Witch, T. Charles Erikson, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Richard III, 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - The Ride Across Lake Constance, T. Charles Erikson, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
  - The Road, T. Charles Erikson, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
  - Romeo and Juliet, T. Charles Erikson, 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Romeo and Juliet, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Sacrophgus, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - The Seagull T., Charles Erikson, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - The Seagull T., Charles Erikson, 1997-1998 (Box 3)
  - Spring Awakening, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - Ste. Carmen of the Main (Box 3)
  - Stage Door Photo Plus, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Subject to Fits, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - The Suicide, P. J. Penders, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
  - Summer Folk, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
  - Tartuffe, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
  - The Tempest, P. J. Penders, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Three Sisters, T. Charles Erikson, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Three Sisters, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Timon of Athens, T. Charles Erikson, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
  - Titus Andronicus, P. J. Penders, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Toms Suite Photo Plus, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Troy Women, T. Charles Erikson, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
  - True Blue and Trembling, P.J. Penders, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Twelfth Night, 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Twelfth Night, T. Charles Erikson, 1998-1999 (Box 4)
  - The Visit, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - The Vultures, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - Waiting for Godot, T. Charles Erikson, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - Watertown Primary, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - Women Beware, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
    - Winter's Tale, 1981-1982 (Box 4)
  - Yerma, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
- Negatives, contact sheets and slides of theatrical productions, 1983-2000; Accession 2004-A-060
  - Contact Sheets- slides "Rice Boy" and "Tree" (Box 1)
  - Yale Repretory Theatre
    - Negatives: Heartbreak; Ghosts; Winters Tale; Cemetery; Memento; Apoc; Exact Exchange; A Walk in the Woods; Eliza, 1986-87 (Box 1)
    - Winterfest 9: Contact Sheets- Slides: Wall of Water; My House Play; Interrogating the Nude; The Beach; Starting Monday; Phaedra and Hippolytus, 1987-88 (Box 1)
  - Way of the World New Release (Box 1)
  - Season Collateral
    - 1999-2000 (Box 1)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 1)
  - Yale Repretory Theatre
    - Contact Sheets
      - Imaginary Invalid; Betrayal; A Cup of Coffee; Curse of the Starving Glass; Richard III; Geography, 1999-2000 (Box 2)
    - Winterfest Negatives: Stitchers; Child's Tale; Crazy from the Heart; Union Boxes, 1996 (Box 2)
    - Contact Sheets
      - Galileo; Measure for Measure; The Glass Menagerie; Hay Fever, 1998-1999 (Box 2)
      - Geography; Candida; Splash Hatch on the Going Down; A Midsummer Night's Dream; The Cure at Troy; Petersburg, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Slides
      - Faculties; Various Classes, Lloyd Richards, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
      - Peter and Wendy; Galileo; Crumbs from the Table of Joy, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
      - Measure for Measure; The Glass Menagerie; Hay Fever, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
      - Geography; Candida; Splash Hatch on the E going Down; A Midsummer Nights Dream; The Cure at Troy; Petersburg, 1997-1998 (Box 3)
      - Imaginary Invalid; Betrayal; A Cup of Coffee, 1999-2000 (Box 3)
      - Curse of the Starving Class; Richard III: Geography, 1999-2000 (Box 3)
  - Best of Advocate Award, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Dwight Edgewood Photos-Materials (Box 4)
- Drama School production scrapbooks and photographs, 1927-1966; Accession 2007-A-022
  - Production scrapbooks
    - 1927 April - 1932 April (Box 1)
    - 1932 October - 1933 December (Box 1)
    - 1934 July - 1944 June (Box 1)
    - 1934 October - 1936 August (Box 1)
    - 1936 August - 1939 May (Box 1)
    - 1939 November - 1943 February (Box 1)
    - 1943 July - 1945 June (Box 1)
    - 1945 September - 1946 June (Box 1)
    - 1946 May - 1947 June (Box 2)
    - 1947 April - 1948 June (Box 2)
    - 1953 April - 1954 October (Box 2)
    - 1954 November - 1955 November (Box 2)
    - 1956 February - 1956 May (Box 2)
    - 1956 June - 1957 May (Box 2)
    - 1957 February - 1958 May (Box 2)
    - 1958 April - 1959 May (Box 2)
    - 1959 February - 1960 April (Box 3)
    - 1960 February - 1961 January (Box 3)
    - 1961 January 20 - 1961 December 11 (Box 3)
    - 1961 December - 1962 May (Box 3)
    - 1962 May - 1963 April (Box 3)
    - 1963 April - 1964 February (Box 3)
    - 1964 January - 1965 March (Box 3)
    - 1965 March 29 - 1965 July 25 (Box 3)
    - 1965 September 3 - 1965 November 21 (Box 3)
    - 1965 December 1 - 1966 March (Box 3)
    - 1948 January - 1953 April (Box 4)
  - Production photographs, 1929-1961 (Box 4)
  - Production slides, 1961-1963, undated (Box 5)
- Slides of Yale School of Drama productions, circa 1960s; Accession 2007-A-102
  - Tempest photo project [35mm color slides], circa 1960s (Box 1)
  - He Who Must Die [35mm color slides] (2 sets), circa 1960s (Box 1)
- Photographs of Yale School of Drama productions, 1966-1992; Accession 2008-A-071
  - Viet Rock, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Prometheus Bound, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - The Bacchae, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Volpone, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Coriolanus, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
  - We Bombed in New Haven, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
  - Tis Pity She's a Whore, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Three Sisters, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
  - Greatshot, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - Story Theatre, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 18-20)
  - God Bless, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - They Told Me You Came This Way, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Great Chinese Revolution, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 23-25)
  - Saved, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 26-28)
  - Living Theatre (Mysteries and Smaller Pieces, Antigone, Frankenstein, Paradies Now), 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 29-30)
  - Don Juan, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 31-32)
  - The Rivals, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 33-35)
  - Government Inspector, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 36-38)
  - Crimes and Crimes, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 39-40)
  - Ovid's Metamophoses, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 41-43)
  - Macbeth, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Where Has Tommy Flowers Gone?, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Woyzeck, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 46-47)
  - Stops, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 48-49)
  - The Revenger's Tragedy, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Passion, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 7 Deadly Sins, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 52-53)
  - The Mirror, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Shlemiel the First, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 55-56)
  - Mahagonny, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Caligula, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 58-59)
  - Life is a Dream, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - The Big House, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - When We Dead Awaken, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - I Married You for the Fun of It, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Baal, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Are You Now or Have You Ever Been, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - The Bougeois Gentleman, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - A Break in the Sun, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Lear, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - In the Clap Shack, 1972-1972 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Darkroom, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 70-71)
  - Shaft of Love, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Geography of a Horse Dreamer, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - The Tubs, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 74-76)
  - An Evening with Dead Essex, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 77-78)
  - Watergate Classics, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 79-81)
  - Story Theatre: Conrad's Victory, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - The Possessed, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Happy End, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 84-85)
  - A Moon for the Misbegotten, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - The Father, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 87-88)
  - General Gorgeous, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Bingo, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 90-91)